<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Human Recon on Offensive Security Cheatsheet</title>
    <link>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Human Recon on Offensive Security Cheatsheet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E-mails</title>
      <link>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/email/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/email/</guid>
      <description>Online tools # Domain e-mail syntax finder https://www.email-format.com https://hunter.io # E-mail validator https://tools.verifyemailaddress.io/ http://mailtester.com https://dnslytics.com/email-test https://verify-email.org/ 
The Harvester # theHarvester is a famous OSINT and scrapping tool for passiv recon on targets # Using API keys will highly increase results Usage: theharvester options -d: Domain to search or company name -b: data source: baidu, bing, bingapi, dogpile, google, googleCSE, googleplus, google-profiles, linkedin, pgp, twitter, vhost, virustotal, threatcrowd, crtsh, netcraft, yahoo, all -s: start in result number X (default: 0) -v: verify host name via dns resolution and search for virtual hosts -f: save the results into an HTML and XML file (both) -n: perform a DNS reverse query on all ranges discovered -c: perform a DNS brute force for the domain name -t: perform a DNS TLD expansion discovery -e: use this DNS server -p: port scan the detected hosts and check for Takeovers (80,443,22,21,8080) -l: limit the number of results to work with(bing goes from 50 to 50 results, google 100 to 100, and pgp doesn\&amp;#39;t use this option) -h: use SHODAN database to query discovered hosts Examples: theharvester -d microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password leaks</title>
      <link>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/leaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/leaks/</guid>
      <description>PwnedOrNot https://github.com/thewhiteh4t/pwnedOrNot.git # Simple python tool used to check haveIbeenpwned leaks for an e-mail or a list # The tool will then check if the dump is accessible (using haveibeenpwned/pastebin) to get passwords python pwnedornot.py -h python pwnedornot.py -e email@test.com python pwnedornot.py -f file.txt Pwndb.py # Tool using onion website http://pwndb2am4tzkvold.onion/ to search leaks and retrieve known passwords python pwndb.py --target email@test.fr python pwndb.py --list file python pwndb.py --target email@test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching Someone</title>
      <link>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/searchingsomeone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/searchingsomeone/</guid>
      <description>Searching People https://i-sight.com/resources/101-osint-resources-for-investigators/ # You can use many online resources to search for people by name, phone number, etc.. Ancestry - Search for genealogy Filae - Search for genealogy, family, relationships... Infobel - Search worldwide people (white pages, yellow pages etc, you can find relations by name) MarketVisual - Map a company organization chart Numberway - Way to find others resources to get phone numbers Pipl - Search engines only for people Spokeo - Search for people information (only in USA) Usersearch - Search engine tool to find someone using pseudo/username Webmii - Search engine that compiles information on one person # Search by photo Tineye # Search on communities and blogs (reddit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skiptracer</title>
      <link>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/skiptracer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/skiptracer/</guid>
      <description>Skiptracer # Tool https://github.com/xillwillx/skiptracer/wiki # It uses some basic python webscraping to compile passive information on a target # Included modules will allow queries for the following : # Phone # Email # Screen names # Real names # Addresses # IP # Hostname # Breach Credentials python skiptracer.py -l phone python skiptracer.py -l email python skiptracer.py -l sn python skiptracer.py -l plate- # Phone Number (FR) https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geolocation</title>
      <link>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/geolocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/open-source-intelligence-osint/human-recon/geolocation/</guid>
      <description>Creepy # Creepy is a tool that performs geolocalization through social network inputs # Written in Python, you get a GUI # It uses modules for social networks # You need to first configurate your plugins (using API key for example) # Then you can start a new person project # You choose your plugins, let the soft searches and then add targets to the global search # Once done, you can start searching (often several minutes) # Then you will get locations on the world map for data found # Possible to export results https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>